<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>No Man Sky on No_Man_Sky</title>
    <link>https://namikxgithub.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in No Man Sky on No_Man_Sky</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://namikxgithub.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://namikxgithub.github.io/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namikxgithub.github.io/about_me/</guid>
      <description>Hi there,
Well here is some stuff you might wanna know about me&amp;hellip;
So, My name is Naman Malik, a Part-time electronics student and a Full-time Maker. Though I am an Electronics student from profession but a Robotics Enthusiast by heart. I have my Keen interests in Robotics, ROS, IOT and developing a taste in Computer Vision. Driven by the idea of Project-based Learing, Eager to tinker with and learn about new Tech and always ready to get my hand dirty on new projects - be it Hardware or Software</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://namikxgithub.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namikxgithub.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Comming Soon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New</title>
      <link>https://namikxgithub.github.io/whats_new/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namikxgithub.github.io/whats_new/</guid>
      <description>6-DOF Servo Arm I, Arduino A Maker&amp;rsquo;s Coffee Table Eyantra Finals 2020 Highlights  I, Arduino About Arduino Day is a worldwide birthday celebration of Arduino – organized directly by the community, or by the Arduino team. It brings people together to share their experiences and learn more about the open-source platform.
So this year, I coordinated with HatchnHack organized the I, Arduino event to acknowledge the open-source Arduino community who encouraged the people to make countless exciting projects over the years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
